{
    "subject": "resource/Carnarvon,_Western_Australia",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Carnarvon",
    "human_readable": "The name of Carnarvon, Western Australia is Carnarvon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9859544634819031,
            "question": "What is the name of Carnarvon, Western Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8008778095245361,
            "question": "What country is Carnarvon in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7307044863700867,
            "question": "Where is Carnarvon located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6375870704650879,
            "question": "Is Carnarvon a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5902736783027649,
            "question": "What state or province is Carnarvon in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5777600407600403,
            "question": "Is there anything famous about Carnarvon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5535908341407776,
            "question": "How would you describe Carnarvon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49349918961524963,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks in Carnarvon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4673239588737488,
            "question": "What is the population of Carnarvon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4438263773918152,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Carnarvon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Carnarvon, Western Australia is Carnarvon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4048_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Carnarvon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4048_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable landmarks in Carnarvon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4048_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Carnarvon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4048_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4048_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can evaluate whether the statement \"The name of Carnarvon, Western Australia is Carnarvon\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's my evaluation:\n\n* The first document mentions \"Carnarvon\" as a city in Western Australia.\n* The remaining 5 documents consistently mention \"Carnarvon\" as a coastal town or city situated approximately 900 kilometres north of Perth, Western Australia. There is no variation in the spelling of the name.\n\nTherefore, my evaluation is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently refer to a place named \"Carnarvon\" in Western Australia. Therefore, the statement that the name of Carnarvon, Western Australia is Carnarvon is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}